<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gotemplate</title><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/</link><description>Recent content on gotemplate</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/all_functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/all_functions/</guid><description>All functions Base go template functions andcalleqgegthtmlindexjslelenltnenotorprintprintfprintlnurlqueryData Conversion DATAHCLJSONTFVARSYAMLdatafromDATAfromDatafromHCLfromHclfromJSONfromJsonfromTFVARSfromTFVarsfromYAMLfromYamlhcljsontfvarstoBashtoHCLtoHcltoIHCLtoIHcltoInternalHCLtoInternalHcltoJSONtoJsontoPrettyHCLtoPrettyHcltoPrettyJSONtoPrettyJsontoPrettyTFVarstoQuotedHCLtoQuotedHcltoQuotedJSONtoQuotedJsontoQuotedTFVarstoTFVarstoYAMLtoYamlyamlData Manipulation StringappendarrayboolcharcontainscontainsStrictcontentdeletedictdictionaryextractfindfindStrictgethashasKeyhasStrictifUndefinitialintersectisEmptyisNilisNullisSetisZerokeykeyslenclistmergenbCharsomitpickpickvpluckprependpushremoveremoveEmptyremoveNilrestreversesafeIndexsetslicestringtupleundefunionuniquniqueunsetvalueswithoutGit functions currentBranchcurrentCommitoriginLogging criticalcriticalfdebugdebugferrorerrorffatalfatalfinfoinfofnoticenoticefpanicpanicftracetracefwarnwarnfwarningwarningfMathematic Bit Operations bandbclearbitwiseANDbitwiseClearbitwiseORbitwiseXORborbxorleftShiftlshiftrightShiftrshiftMathematic Fundamental addcbrtceildimdivdivideexpexp2expm1exponentexponent2floorintint64integerinteger64modmodfmodulomulmultiplypowpow10powerpower10prodproductquotientremremainderroundDownroundUprounddownroundupsubsubtractsumtrunctruncateMathematic Stats averageavgbiggestmaxmaximumminminimumsmallestMathematic Trigonometry acosacosharcCosinearcCosinusarcHyperbolicCosinearcHyperbolicCosinusarcHyperbolicSinearcHyperbolicSinusarcHyperbolicTangentarcSinearcSinusarcTangentarcTangent2asinasinhatanatan2atanhcoscoshcosinecosinusdegdegreefirstBessel0firstBessel1firstBesselNhyperbolicCosinehyperbolicCosinushyperbolicSinehyperbolicSinushyperbolicTangentilogbj0j1jnloglog10log1plog2logbradradiansecondBessel0secondBessel1secondBesselNsinsincossinesineCosinesinhsinussinusCosinustantangenttanhy0y1ynMathematic Utilities absabsolutedecdecimalfrexpgammahexhexahexaDecimalhypothypotenuseisInfisInfinityisNaNldexplgammanextAftersignBitsqrtsquareRoottountilNet curlhttpDochttpDocumenthttpGetOperating systems functions currentDircurrentUserdiffdifferenceexistsexpandfileExistsfileModefileSizefileStatglobgrouphomehomeDirhomeFolderisDirisDirectoryisExecutableisExistisFileisFolderisReadableisWriteablejoinPathlastModlastModificationlastModificationTimelooklookPathmodepwdsavesizestattypeuseruserGroupusernamewhereIswhichwritewriteToOther utilities aIndentaWrapaindentautoIndentautoWrapawrapcentercenteredcolorcoloredcolorlnconcatenhancedformatListididentifieriifindentjoinLinesloremloremIpsummergeListnIndentnindentprintRawrawrawListreCompilerepeatsIndentsindentspaceIndentsplitLinesstripANSIstripColorstripansistriptcolorternarywrapwrappedRuntime aliasaliasesallFunctionsassertassertWarningassertionassertwattrattributesccategoriescompleteExamplescontextcurrentellipsisevalexecexecuteexitfuncfunctionfunctionsgetAttributesgetMethodsgetSignatureincludelocalAliasmethodsraiseraiseErrorrunsignsignaturesubstitutetemplateNamestemplatesuserContextSprig Cryptographic &amp;amp; Security adler32sumbcryptbuildCustomCertdecryptAESderivePasswordencryptAESgenCAgenCAWithKeygenPrivateKeygenSelfSignedCertgenSelfSignedCertWithKeygenSignedCertgenSignedCertWithKeyhtpasswdrandBytessha1sumsha256sumSprig Date agodatedateInZonedateModifydate_in_zonedate_modifydurationdurationRoundhtmlDatehtmlDateInZonenowtoDateunixEpochSprig Default coalescecompactdefaultemptyfromJsonSprigternarySprigtoJsonSprigtoPrettyJsonSprigtoRawJsonSprig Dictionary deepCopydictSprigdiggetSprighasKeySprigkeysSpriglistSprigmergeOverwritemergeSprigomitSprigpickSprigpluckSprigsetSprigtupleSprigunsetSprigvaluesSprigSprig Encoding b32decb32encb64decb64encSprig File Path basecleandirextisAbsosBaseosCleanosDirosExtosIsAbsSprig Flow Control failSprig General GUIDguidhellouuiduuidv4Sprig List allanyappendSprigchunkconcatSprigfirsthasSpriginitialSpriglastprependSprigpushSprigrestSprigreverseSprigsliceSpriguniqSprigSprig Mathematics add1add1faddSprigaddfbiggestSprigceilSprigdivSprigdivffloorSprigmaxSprigmaxfminSprigminfmodSprigmulSprigmulfrandIntroundseqsubSprigsubfuntilStepSprig Network functions getHostByNameSprig OS envexpandenvSprig Reflection deepEqualkindIskindOfkindiskindoftypeIstypeIsLiketypeOftypeistypeisLiketypeofSprig Regex regexFindregexFindAllregexMatchregexQuoteMetaregexReplaceAllregexReplaceAllLiteralregexSplitSprig String Slice joinsortAlphasplitsplitListsplitntoStringsSprig Strings abbrevabbrevbothcamelcasecatcontainsSprighasPrefixhasSuffixindentSpriginitialskebabcaselowernindentSprignospacepluralquoterandAlpharandAlphaNumrandAsciirandNumericrepeatSprigreplaceshufflesnakecasesquotesubstrswapcasetitletoStringtrimtrimAlltrimPrefixtrimSuffixtrimalltruncSpriguntitleupperwrapSprigwrapWithSprig Type Conversion atoifloat64intSprigtoDecimalSprig URL functions urlJoinurlParseSprig Version comparison semversemverCompare</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/base-go-template-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/base-go-template-functions/</guid><description>Base go template functions and func and(arg0 reflect.Value, args ...reflect.Value) reflect.Value Returns the boolean AND of its arguments by returning the first empty argument or the last argument, that is, &amp;quot;and x y&amp;quot; behaves as &amp;quot;if x then y else x&amp;quot;. All the arguments are evaluated. call func call(fn reflect.Value, args ...reflect.Value) reflect.Value Returns the result of calling the first argument, which must be a function, with the remaining arguments as parameters.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/data-conversion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/data-conversion/</guid><description>Data Conversion data func data(data interface{}, context ...interface{}) interface{} Tries to parse the given input string as a data structure. This function supports JSON, HCL and YAML. If the context argument is omitted, the default context is used. Note that this function attempts to template the given input string. This means that if the input string contains gotemplate expressions, those will be evaluated. This behavior is deprecated and will be removed in future versions of gotemplate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/data-manipulation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/data-manipulation/</guid><description>Data Manipulation String func String(value interface{}) String Returns a String class object that allows invoking standard string operations as method. append func append(list interface{}, elements ...interface{}) IGenericList Append new items to an existing list, creating a new list. Aliases push array func array(value interface{}) interface{} Ensures that the supplied argument is an array (if it is already an array/slice, there is no change, if not, the argument is replaced by []interface{} with a single value).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/git-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/git-functions/</guid><description>Git functions currentBranch func currentBranch(path string) string Returns the name of the currently checked out git branch at the given path currentCommit func currentCommit(path string) string Returns the hash of the currently checked out git commit at the given path origin func origin(path string) string Returns the git origin remote URL at the given path</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/logging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/logging/</guid><description>Logging critical func critical(args ...interface{}) string Deprecated: Use error instead. Logs a message using ERROR log level (2). Aliases criticalf debug func debug(args ...interface{}) string Logs a message using DEBUG as log level (5). Aliases debugf error func error(args ...interface{}) string Logs a message using ERROR as log level (2). Aliases errorf fatal func fatal(args ...interface{}) string Logs a message using FATAL as log level (1) followed by a call to os.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-bit-operations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-bit-operations/</guid><description>Mathematic Bit Operations band func band(arg1 interface{}, arg2 interface{}, args ...interface{}) interface{} Returns the result of bitwise AND operation (&amp;amp;) between all arguments. Aliases bitwiseAND bclear func bclear(arg1 interface{}, arg2 interface{}, args ...interface{}) interface{} Performs a bitwise clear (&amp;amp;^) between all arguments. Aliases bitwiseClear bor func bor(arg1 interface{}, arg2 interface{}, args ...interface{}) interface{} Performs a bitwise OR (|) between all arguments. Aliases bitwiseOR bxor func bxor(arg1 interface{}, arg2 interface{}, args .</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-fundamental/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-fundamental/</guid><description>Mathematic Fundamental add func add(arg1 interface{}, args ...interface{}) interface{} Returns the result of the addition of all arguments. Aliases sum cbrt func cbrt(x interface{}) interface{} Returns the cube root of x. Special cases are: cbrt(±0) = ±0 cbrt(±Inf) = ±Inf cbrt(NaN) = NaN ceil func ceil(x interface{}) interface{} Returns the least integer value greater than or equal to x. Special cases are: ceil(±0) = ±0 ceil(±Inf) = ±Inf ceil(NaN) = NaN Aliases roundUp roundup dim func dim(x interface{}, y interface{}) interface{} Returns the maximum of x-y or 0.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-stats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-stats/</guid><description>Mathematic Stats avg func avg(arg1 interface{}, args ...interface{}) interface{} Returns the average value of the specified numbers. Aliases average max func max(x ...interface{}) interface{} Returns the larger of x or y. Special cases are: max(x, +Inf) = max(+Inf, x) = +Inf max(x, NaN) = max(NaN, x) = NaN max(+0, ±0) = max(±0, +0) = +0 max(-0, -0) = -0 Aliases maximum biggest min func min(x ...interface{}) interface{} Returns the smaller of x or y.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-trigonometry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-trigonometry/</guid><description>Mathematic Trigonometry acos func acos(x interface{}) interface{} Returns the arccosine, in radians, of x. Special case is: acos(x) = NaN if x &amp;amp;lt; -1 or x &amp;gt; 1 Aliases arcCosine arcCosinus Examples Razor: @ceil(acos(0.5) / 3.1416 * 180) Template: {{ ceil (mul (div (acos 0.5) 3.1416) 180) }} Result: 60 acosh func acosh(x interface{}) interface{} Returns the inverse hyperbolic cosine of x. Special cases are: acosh(+Inf) = +Inf acosh(x) = NaN if x &amp;amp;lt; 1 acosh(NaN) = NaN Aliases arcHyperbolicCosine arcHyperbolicCosinus asin func asin(x interface{}) interface{} Returns the arcsine, in radians, of x.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-utilities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/mathematic-utilities/</guid><description>Mathematic Utilities abs func abs(x interface{}) interface{} Returns the absolute value of x. Special cases are: abs(±Inf) = +Inf abs(NaN) = NaN Aliases absolute Examples Razor: @abs(0) Template: {{ abs 0 }} Result: 0 Razor: @abs(22) Template: {{ abs 22 }} Result: 22 Razor: @abs(-10) Template: {{ abs -10 }} Result: 10 dec func dec(arg1 interface{}) interface{} Converts an hexadecimal number to decimal. Aliases decimal frexp func frexp(f interface{}) interface{} Breaks f into a normalized fraction and an integral power of two.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/net/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/net/</guid><description>Net httpDoc func httpDoc(url interface{}) interface{} Returns http document returned by supplied URL. Aliases httpDocument curl httpGet func httpGet(url interface{}) *http.Response Returns http get response from supplied URL.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/operating-systems-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/operating-systems-functions/</guid><description>Operating systems functions diff func diff(text1 interface{}, text2 interface{}) interface{} Returns a colored string that highlight differences between supplied texts. Aliases difference exists func exists(filename interface{}) bool Determines if a file exists or not. Aliases fileExists isExist glob func glob(args ...interface{}) IGenericList Returns the expanded list of supplied arguments (expand *[]? on filename). Aliases expand group func group() *user.Group Returns the current user group information (user.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/other-utilities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/other-utilities/</guid><description>Other utilities center func center(width interface{}, args ...interface{}) string Returns the concatenation of supplied arguments centered within width. Aliases centered color func color(args ...interface{}) string Colors the rendered string. The first arguments are interpretated as color attributes until the first non color attribute. Attributes are case insensitive. Valid attributes are: Reset, Bold, Faint, Italic, Underline, BlinkSlow, BlinkRapid, ReverseVideo, Concealed, CrossedOut Valid color are: Black, Red, Green, Yellow, Blue, Magenta, Cyan, White Color can be prefixed by: Fg: Meaning foreground (Fg is assumed if not specified) FgHi: Meaning high intensity forgeround Bg: Meaning background&amp;quot; BgHi: Meaning high intensity background Aliases colored enhanced colorln func colorln(args .</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/runtime/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/runtime/</guid><description>Runtime alias func alias(name string, function string, source interface{}, args ...interface{}) string Defines an alias (go template function) using the function (exec, run, include, template). Executed in the context of the caller. aliases func aliases() []string Returns the list of all functions that are simply an alias of another function. allFunctions func allFunctions() []string Returns the list of all available functions. assert func assert(test interface{}, message ...interface{}) string Raises a formated error if the test condition is false.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-cryptographic-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-cryptographic-security/</guid><description>Sprig Cryptographic &amp;amp; Security adler32sum func adler32sum(input string) string Computes Adler-32 checksum. bcrypt func bcrypt(arg1 string) string Receives a string, and generates its bcrypt hash. buildCustomCert func buildCustomCert(base64Cert string, base64PrivateKey string) sprig.certificate Allows customizing the certificate. decryptAES func decryptAES(encoded string, key string) string Receives a base64 string encoded by the AES-256 CBC algorithm and returns the decoded text. derivePassword func derivePassword(counter uint32, passwordType string, password string, user string, site string) string Derive a specific password based on some shared 'master password' constraints.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-date/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-date/</guid><description>Sprig Date ago func ago(date interface{}) string The ago function returns duration from time.Now in seconds resolution. date func date(fmt string, date interface{}) string The date function formats a date [format](https://golang.org/pkg/time/#Time.Format). dateInZone func dateInZone(fmt string, date interface{}, zone string) string Same as date, but with a timezone. Aliases date_in_zone dateModify func dateModify(fmt string, date time.Time) time.Time The dateModify takes a modification and a date and returns the timestamp. date_modify func date_modify(fmt string, date time.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-default/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-default/</guid><description>Sprig Default coalesce func coalesce(args ...interface{}) interface{} Takes a list of values and returns the first non-empty one. compact func compact(list interface{}) []interface{} Removes entries with empty values. default func default(default interface{}, value ...interface{}) interface{} Set a simple default value. empty func empty(value interface{}) bool Returns true if the given value is considered empty. fromJsonSprig func fromJsonSprig(arg1 string) interface{} Decodes a JSON document into a structure. If the input cannot be decoded as JSON the function will return an empty string.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-dictionary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-dictionary/</guid><description>Sprig Dictionary deepCopy func deepCopy(arg1 interface{}) interface{} Takes a value and makes a deep copy of the value. dictSprig func dictSprig(args ...interface{}) map[string]interface{} Create a dictionary. Aliases dict dig func dig(key... ...interface{}) interface{} Traverses a nested set of dicts, selecting keys from a list of values. It returns a default value if any of the keys are not found at the associated dict. getSprig func getSprig(dict map[string]interface{}, key string) interface{} Given a map and a key, get the value from the map.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-encoding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-encoding/</guid><description>Sprig Encoding b32dec func b32dec(arg1 string) string Decode with Base32. b32enc func b32enc(arg1 string) string Encode with Base32. b64dec func b64dec(arg1 string) string Decode with Base64. b64enc func b64enc(arg1 string) string Encode with Base64.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-file-path/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-file-path/</guid><description>Sprig File Path base func base(arg1 string) string Returns the last element of a path. clean func clean(arg1 string) string Clean up a path. dir func dir(arg1 string) string Returns the directory, stripping the last part of the path. ext func ext(arg1 string) string Returns the file extension. isAbs func isAbs(arg1 string) bool Check whether a file path is absolute. osBase func osBase(arg1 string) string Return the last element of a filepath.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-flow-control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-flow-control/</guid><description>Sprig Flow Control fail func fail(arg1 string) string Unconditionally returns an empty string and an error with the specified text. This is useful in scenarios where other conditionals have determined that template rendering should fail.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-general/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-general/</guid><description>Sprig General hello func hello() string Simple hello by Sprig uuidv4 func uuidv4() string Returns a new UUID of the v4 (randomly generated) type. Aliases uuid guid GUID</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-list/</guid><description>Sprig List all func all(arg1 interface{}, args ...interface{}) []interface{} Filters items out of a list. Aliases without any func any(args ...interface{}) bool Takes a list of values and returns true if any values are non-empty. appendSprig func appendSprig(arg1 interface{}, arg2 interface{}) []interface{} Append a new item to an existing list, creating a new list. Aliases append chunk func chunk(nbChunks int, list interface{}) [][]interface{} Split a list into chunks of given size, use chunk size list.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-mathematics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-mathematics/</guid><description>Sprig Mathematics add1 func add1(arg1 interface{}) int64 Increments a value by 1. add1f func add1f(arg1 interface{}) float64 Increments a float value by 1. addSprig func addSprig(args ...interface{}) int64 Sum numbers with `add`. Accepts two or more inputs. Aliases add addf func addf(args ...interface{}) float64 Sum float numbers with `add`. Accepts two or more inputs. ceilSprig func ceilSprig(arg1 interface{}) float64 Returns the greatest float value greater than or equal to input value.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-network-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-network-functions/</guid><description>Sprig Network functions getHostByName func getHostByName(name string) string Receives a domain name and returns the ip address.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-os/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-os/</guid><description>Sprig OS env func env(arg1 string) string Reads an environment variable. expandenv func expandenv(arg1 string) string Substitute environment variables in a string.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-reflection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-reflection/</guid><description>Sprig Reflection deepEqual func deepEqual(arg1 interface{}, arg2 interface{}) bool returns true if two values are deeply equal. kindIs func kindIs(arg1 string, arg2 interface{}) bool Let you verify that a value is a particular kind. Aliases kindis kindOf func kindOf(arg1 interface{}) string Returns the kind of an object. Aliases kindof typeIs func typeIs(arg1 string, arg2 interface{}) bool Like `kindIs`, but for types. Aliases typeis typeIsLike func typeIsLike(arg1 string, arg2 interface{}) bool Works as `typeIs`, except that it also dereferences pointers.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-regex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-regex/</guid><description>Sprig Regex regexFind func regexFind(regex string, str string) string Returns the first (left most) match of the regular expression in the input string. regexFindAll func regexFindAll(regex string, str string, n int) []string Returns a slice of all matches of the regular expression in the input string. regexMatch func regexMatch(regex string, str string) bool Returns true if the input string matches the regular expression. regexQuoteMeta func regexQuoteMeta(arg1 string) string Returns a string that escapes all regular expression metacharacters inside the argument text; the returned string is a regular expression matching the literal text regexReplaceAll func regexReplaceAll(regex string, str string, repl string) string Returns a copy of the input string, replacing matches of the Regexp with the replacement string replacement.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-string-slice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-string-slice/</guid><description>Sprig String Slice join func join(separator string, list interface{}) string Joins a list of strings into a single string, with the given separator. sortAlpha func sortAlpha(list interface{}) []string Sorts a list of strings into alphabetical (lexicographical) order. split func split(separator string, str string) map[string]string Splits a string into a `dict`. It is designed to make it easy to use template dot notation for accessing members splitList func splitList(separator string, str string) []string Splits a string into a list of strings.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-strings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-strings/</guid><description>Sprig Strings abbrev func abbrev(width int, str string) string Truncates a string with ellipses (...). abbrevboth func abbrevboth(left int, right int, str string) string Abbreviates both sides with ellipses (...). camelcase func camelcase(str string) string Converts string from snake_case to CamelCase. cat func cat(args ...interface{}) string Concatenates multiple strings together into one, separating them with spaces. containsSprig func containsSprig(substr string, str string) bool Tests to see if one string is contained inside of another.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-type-conversion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-type-conversion/</guid><description>Sprig Type Conversion atoi func atoi(str string) int Convert a string to an integer. float64 func float64(value interface{}) float64 Convert to a `float64`. intSprig func intSprig(value interface{}) int Convert to an `int` at the system's width. Aliases int toDecimal func toDecimal(octalString interface{}) int64 Convert a unix octal to a 'int64'.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-url-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-url-functions/</guid><description>Sprig URL functions urlJoin func urlJoin(dictionary map[string]interface{}) string Joins map (produced by `urlParse`) to produce URL string. urlParse func urlParse(uri string) map[string]interface{} Parses string for URL and produces dict with URL parts.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-version-comparison/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/functions_reference/sprig-version-comparison/</guid><description>Sprig Version comparison semver func semver(version string) *semver.Version Parses a string into a Semantic Version. semverCompare func semverCompare(constraints string, version string) bool A more robust comparison function is provided as semverCompare. This version supports version ranges.</description></item></channel></rss>