<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gotemplate</title><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/basics/</link><description>Recent content on Gotemplate</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CLI Usage</title><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/basics/cli_usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/basics/cli_usage/</guid><description>usage: ./gotemplate [&amp;lt;flags&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;command&amp;gt; [&amp;lt;args&amp;gt; ...] An extended template processor for go. See: https://coveo.github.io/gotemplate for complete documentation. Flags: -h, --help Show context-sensitive help (also try --help-man). or set _GOTEMPLATE_HELP --color Force rendering of colors event if output is redirected or set _GOTEMPLATE_COLOR (alias: --c) -v, --version Get the current version of gotemplate --base Turn off all addons (they could then be enabled explicitly) or set _GOTEMPLATE_BASE --razor Razor Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_RAZOR (off: --no-razor) --extension Extension Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_EXTENSION (alias: --ext) (off: --next, --no-ext, --no-extension) --math Math Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_MATH (off: --no-math) --sprig Sprig Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_SPRIG (off: --no-sprig) --data Data Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_DATA (off: --no-data) --logging Logging Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_LOGGING (off: --no-logging) --runtime Runtime Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_RUNTIME (off: --no-runtime) --utils Utils Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_UTILS (off: --no-utils) --net Net Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_NET (off: --nnet, --no-net) --os OS Addon (ON by default) or set _GOTEMPLATE_OS (off: --no-os, --nos) Args: [&amp;lt;templates&amp;gt;] Template files or commands to process Commands: help [&amp;lt;command&amp;gt;.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/basics/functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/basics/functions/</guid><description>Base go template functions and gt le not println call html len or urlquery eq index lt print ge js ne printf Data Conversion data toHcl toPrettyJson toQuotedTFVars hcl toInternalHcl toPrettyTFVars toTFVars json toJson toQuotedHcl toYaml toBash toPrettyHcl toQuotedJson yaml Data Manipulation String extract key pluck undef append get keys prepend union array hasKey lenc rest unique bool initial list reverse unset char intersect merge safeIndex values contains isNil omit set without content isSet pick slice dict isZero pickv string Logging critical error info panic debug fatal notice warning Mathematic Bit Operations band bor lshift bclear bxor rshift Mathematic Fundamental add div floor pow trunc cbrt exp mod pow10 ceil exp2 modf rem dim expm1 mul sub Mathematic Stats avg max min Mathematic Trigonometry acos atanh j1 logb tanh acosh cos jn rad y0 asin cosh log sin y1 asinh deg log10 sincos yn atan ilogb log1p sinh atan2 j0 log2 tan Mathematic Utilities abs gamma isInf lgamma sqrt dec hex isNaN nextAfter to frexp hypot ldexp signBit until Net httpDoc httpGet Operating systems functions diff home isReadable mode stat exists isDir isWriteable pwd user glob isExecutable lastMod save username group isFile lookPath size Other utilities center formatList indent mergeList sIndent color id joinLines nIndent splitLines concat iif lorem repeat wrap Runtime alias categories func getSignature substitute aliases current function include templateNames allFunctions ellipsis functions localAlias templates assert exec getAttributes raise assertWarning exit getMethods run Sprig Cryptographic &amp;amp; Security http://masterminds.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/basics/functions_long/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://coveooss.github.io/gotemplate/docs/basics/functions_long/</guid><description>Functions Base go template functions // Returns the boolean AND of its arguments by returning the first empty argument or the last argument, that is, &amp;quot;and x y&amp;quot; behaves as &amp;quot;if x then y else x&amp;quot;. All the arguments are evaluated. func and(arg0 reflect.Value, args ...reflect.Value) reflect.Value // Returns the result of calling the first argument, which must be a function, with the remaining arguments as parameters. Thus &amp;quot;call .</description></item></channel></rss>